A Guide to the Wallace Company Records, 1783-1975 (bulk 1875-1945)
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Subject Files, 1783-1975., Extent: 40 boxes. (Box 23-62)
  - Seaboard Citizens National Bank - Dover Production, 1934-1936 (Box 48, Folder 4-6)
  - L. W. Sherman and Company, 1895 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Shingle Memoranda, 1884=1886 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Skiffing Receipts, 1885 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Slabaugh, Joseph - Rental Agreement, 1936-1937 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Southern Immigration Association (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Southern Mutual Insurance Company, 1870-1871 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - The Southern Planter, 1894-1895 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Southern Produce Company Stock Certificate, 1915 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Southern Seminary (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Southern States Invoices, 1943-1944 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Soybeans (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - George F. Spencer - Account of Sales of Dover Corn Crop, 1906 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Standard Oil Company, 1896-1897 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - State Farm Auto Insurance, 1935 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Stationary, Letterhead (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - John Staum and Sons, 1895 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Stave Accounts, 1875 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Stearns Motor Manufacturing Company, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Stewart Lease, 1916 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Stock Certificates, 1890 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Subpoenas (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Suit Papers - John L. Roper Company v. Richmond Cedar Works (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Sunray Drainage District, 1925 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Supervisor of Elections - Instructions, etc., 1888-1894 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Survey Abstracts (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Surveys, 1783 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Surveys, 1795 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Surveys, 1800-1809 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Surveys, 1810-1819 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Surveys, 1820-1829 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Surveys, 1830-1839 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Surveys, 1840-1849 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Surveys, 1870-1879 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Surveys, 1880-1889 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Surveys, 1890-1899 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Surveys, 1900-1910 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Surveys, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Swamp Lands (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Swamp Memoranda (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Sweet Potatoes (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Tank Information (Specifications, Prices, etc.) (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Tatem, C. E. - Drafts, Orders, 1873 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Tatem, C. E. - Drafts, Orders, 1874-1875 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Tax Assessor Papers (Box 50, Folder 7-8)
  - Tax Assessor Reimbursement Accounts (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Tax Information and Publications (Box 50, Folder 10-12)
  - Tax Return, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Tax Return, 1943 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1864 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1870 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1871 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1872 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1878 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1879 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1880 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1881 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1882 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1883-1897 (Box 51, Folder 1-15)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1901 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1902 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1903 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1904 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1906 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1907 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1909 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1910 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1911 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1912 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1913 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1914 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1929 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1932 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1938 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1946 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Tax Tickets and Receipts (North Carolina), 1885-1893 (Box 52, Folder 1-9)
  - Telegraph Pole Measurements (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Telegraph and Telephone Cross Arms - Costs, Inventories, etc. (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Tenant Rental Agreements, 1936 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Title Abstracts (Box 52, Folder 13-14)
  - Title Matters (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Toll Rates - Chesapeake and Delaware Canal, 1883 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Townsend Nurseries (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Trade Cards (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Trial Balances, 1875 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Trial Balances, 1890 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Trial Balances, 1893 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Trial Balances, 1901 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Trip Expenses, 1874 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Trip Expenses, 1889 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Trust Deed Notes, 1924 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Trust Deed Notes, 1929 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - United States Express Company, 1910-1911 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - U. S. Geological Survey (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Accounts, 1894-1898 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Accounts, 1 May 1898 - 30 April 1899 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Accounts, 1 May 1899 - 30 April 1900 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Accounts, 1 May 1900 - 30 April 1901 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Accounts, 1 May 1901 - 30 April 1902 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Accounts, 1 May 1902 - 30 April 1903 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Accounts, 1 May 1903 - 30 April 1904 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Accounts, 1 May 1904 - 30 April 1905 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Accounts, 1 May 1905 - 30 April 1906 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Accounts, 1 May 1906 - 30 April 1907 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Accounts of Sales, 1898-1899 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Accounts of Sales, 1901-1904 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Accounts of Sales, 1905-1907 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Accounts of Sales - Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - C. R. Van de Carr - Correspondence, 1895 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Crop Improvement Association, 1942-1944 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Fire and Marine Insurance Company (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Virginia National Bank (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Saw Mill Company, 1900 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Virginia State Insurance Company, 1889 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Wallace Brothers (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Wallace, William, 1895 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Wallaceton Colored School House, 1884 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Warren, W. J., 1885 (January-June) (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Warren, W. J., 1885 (July-December) (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Warren, W. J., 1886 (January-June) (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Warren, W. J., 1886 (July-December) (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Warren, W. J. - Reports, 1882 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Warren's Hauling Equipment, Logs, etc., 1885-1889 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Water Tank, 1941 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Wedding Announcements and Invitations (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Weight Tickets (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Wick and Brother, 1895 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Will of William Boushell, 1793 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Will of Dr. Ferebee (Extracts), 1884 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Will of James S. Seguine, 1868 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - William and Mary (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - J. G. Womble's Sons, 1915-1916 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - T. W. Wood and Sons, 1895 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Product Catalogs and Equipment Instructions (Box 55)
  - Maps, Tourist Brochures, Garden and Seed Catalogs (Box 56)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 57-58)
  - Ephemera (Box 59)
  - Oversize - American Legion of Honor Journal, 1892 (Box 60)
  - Oversize - Bills of Lading and Freight Tickets (Box 60)
  - Oversize - Boat Measurements, 1887 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Oversize - Carolina Seed Company, 1893 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Oversize - Check Register, 1891-1893 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Oversize - Churchland Academy Certificate (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Oversize - Deeds (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Oversize - Income Tax Return, 1929 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Oversize - Income Tax Return, 1943 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Oversize - Income Tax Return (Blank Form), 1944 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Oversize - Frank H. Lester Fruits, 1898 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Oversize - Lighter Memoranda, 1874 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Oversize - Lumber Inventories, 1885 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Oversize - Mutual Reserve Fund Life Association, 1889-1890 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Oversize - Mutual Reserve Fund Life Association, 1893 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Oversize - Portsmouth Insurance Company (Newsome Norfleet), 1883 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Oversize - Queen Insurance Company, 1886 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Oversize - Survey (Letter re:), 1845 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Oversize - Tungtite Pistons (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Oversize - Virginia State Insurance Company (Samuel Warren), 1889 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Oversize - Wallace Company Bond and Coupons (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Oversize - Wallace Property Boundaries (Blueprint), 1941 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Oversize - American Legion of Honor (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Oversize - House Tickets (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Oversize - Insurance Policies (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Oversize - Japanese Art Tissue Samples (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Oversize - Land Grants (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Oversize - Lumber and Crop Memoranda (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Oversize - Order of Tonti, 1888-1889 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Oversize - Pay Rolls (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Oversize - Piston Research Corporation Drawings (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Oversize - Postmaster Commission, 1890 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Oversize - Producers' Prices Current, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Oversize - Surveys (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Series III. Financial Records, 1840-1962., Extent: 27 boxes and 249 volumes.
  The financial records include account and memorandum books, accounts payable, accounts of sales, bank books, card books, check registers, memoranda and cash accounts, monthly time books, and numerous ledgers.
  Accounts payable contain invoices from various merchants for business and household goods purchased, including groceries, clothing, tuition, medical services, tolls and freight bills, livestock, repairs, labor, hardware, fertilizer, seed, and hardware items. Many of the invoices are for items that were purchased and later sold in the family-owned store at Wallaceton.
  The accounts of sales contain correspondence and financial statements detailing payments for lumber, shingles, railroad ties, rails, and later potatoes, corn, hay, and onions purchased from Wallace and Son and The Wallace Company, and later sold by various commission merchants, as well as for those products purchased by individuals.
  The memoranda and cash accounts are weekly diary notations by John G. Wallace, begun after the failure of Bain and Brother, which include detailed accounts of business and personal expenses and activities, including summaries of trips, meetings, employee work activities, weather conditions, as well as itemized purchases of household goods, and any other expenses incurred during the week. There are also "to-do" lists, and the files occasionally include merchant invoices and receipts.
  The monthly time books include employee name, hours worked per day, total time for the month, rate of pay, amount paid, and any additional notes.
  Also contained in the financial records are various business ledgers, including Bain and Brother accounts with Wallace and Son, card registers, cash ledgers, day books, "Dover" and "Glencoe" record books, job books and petty accounts, letter books, merchandise day books, petty cash ledgers, minute book of The Wallace Company, hands books, time books, and time reports from "Dover."
  - Account and Memorandum Books (Pocket Size) (Box 63)
  - Accounts Payable, 1840-1889 (Box 64, Folder 1-38)
  - Accounts Payable, 1890 (May) - 1891 (April) (Box 65, Folder 1-12)
  - Accounts Payable, 1891 (May) - 1892 (April) (Box 66, Folder 1-12)
  - Accounts Payable, 1892 (May) - 1893 (June) (Box 67, Folder 1-14)
  - Accounts Payable, 1893 (July) - 1894 (August) (Box 68, Folder 1-14)
  - Accounts Payable, 1894 (September) - 1895 (October) (Box 69, Folder 1-14)
  - Accounts Payable, 1895 (November) - 1897 (March) (Box 70, Folder 1-17)
  - Accounts Payable, 1897 (April) - 1898 (December) (Box 71, Folder 1-21)
  - Accounts Payable, 1899 (January) - 1902 (April) (Box 72, Folder 1-18)
  - Accounts Payable, 1902 (May) - 1903 (February) (Box 73, Folder 1-10)
  - Accounts Payable, 1903 (March) - 1904 (July) (Box 74, Folder 1-13)
  - Accounts Payable, 1904 (August) - 1905 (December) (Box 75, Folder 1-17)
  - Accounts Payable, 1906 (January) - 1907 (May) (Box 76, Folder 1-17)
  - Accounts Payable, 1907 (June) - 1962 (Box 77, Folder 1-39)
  - Accounts Payable, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 40)
  - Accounts of Sales, 1870 - 1887 (August) (Box 78, Folder 1-67)
  - Accounts of Sales, 1888-1937 (Box 79, Folder 1-55)
  - Bank Books, Card Books, Check Registers (Box 80)
  - Memoranda and Cash Accounts, 1885-1888 (Box 81, Folder 1-46)
  - Memoranda and Cash Accounts, 1889-1892 (Box 82, Folder 1-48)
  - Memoranda and Cash Accounts, 1893-1895 (Box 83, Folder 1-37)
  - Memoranda and Cash Accounts, 1896-1898 (Box 84, Folder 1-36)
  - Memoranda and Cash Accounts, 1899-1903 (Box 85, Folder 1-40)
  - Memoranda and Cash Accounts, 1904-1908 (April) (Box 86, Folder 1-53)
  - Time Books 1885-1921 (Box 87-89)
  - Account Ledger, 1876-1877 (Volume 2)
  - Account Ledger, 1878-1879 (Volume 3)
  - Account Ledger, 1880 (Volume 4)
  - Account Ledger, 1884-1885 (Volume 5)
  - Account Ledger, 1919-1921 (Volume 8)
  - Bain and Brother in account with Wallace and Son, 1876-1877 (Volume 9)
  - Bain and Brother in account with Wallace and Son, 1879 (Volume 10)
  - Bain and Brother in account with Wallace and Son, 1881-1882 (Volume 11)
  - Bain and Brother in account with Wallace and Son, 1882-1884 (Volume 12)
  - Bain and Brother in account with Wallace and Son, 1884-1885 (Volume 13)
  - Bank Account Receipts and Disbursements, 1928-1931 (Volume 14)
  - Bills and Notes Payable, 1881-1884 (Volume 15)
  - Card Register, 1879-1880 (Volume 16)
  - Card Register, 1880-1882 (Volume 17)
  - Card Book, 1 September 1882 - 31 December 1883 (Volume 18)
  - Card Register, 1884-1885 (Volume 19)
  - Cash Ledger, 1866-1871 (Volume 20)
  - Cash Ledger, 1877-1882 (Volume 21)
  - Cash Book, 1884-1885 (Volume 22)
  - Cash Ledger, 1885-1887 (Volume 23)
  - Cash Ledger, 1887 (Volume 249)
  - Cash Ledger, 1887-1889 (Volume 24)
  - Cash Book, 1890 (Volume 25)
  - Cash Book, 1892-1893 (Volume 26)
  - Cash Ledger, 1893-1895 (Volume 117)
  - Cash Ledger, 1894-1895 (Volume 27)
  - Cash Book, 1895-1903 (Volume 28)
  - Cash Ledger, 1896-1898 (Volume 29)
  - Cash Book, 1898-1900 (Volume 30)
  - Cash Book, 1903-1908 (Volume 31)
  - Cash Book, 1910 (Volume 32)
  - Cash Book, 1912-1914 (Volume 33)
  - Cash Book, 1915-1916 (Volume 34)
  - Cash Book, 1915-1918 (Volume 35)
  - Cash Ledger, 1928-1930 (Volume 36)
  - County Treasurer's Record Book, 1936-1937 (Volume 37)
  - Crop Shipments Ledger, 1912-1921 (Volume 38)
  - Cross Canal Book, 1871 (Volume 39)
  - Day Book, 1 June 1868 - 31 December 1869 (Volume 40)
  - Day Book No. 1, 1 January 1879 - 6 March 1879 (Volume 41)
  - Day Book No. 2, 7 March 1879 - 24 May 1879 (Volume 42)
  - Day Book, 16 October 1879 - 31 December 1879 (Volume 43)
  - Day Book, 20 March 1880-29 May 1880 (Volume 44)
  - Day Book No. 3, 31 May 1880 - 1 August 1880 (Volume 45)
  - Day Book No. 4, 1 August 1880 - 1 October 1880 (Volume 46)
  - Day Book No. 5, 1 October 1880 - 31 December 1880 (Volume 47)
  - Day Book, 1 January 1881 - 31 March 1881 (Volume 48)
  - Day Book No. 2, 1 April 1881 - 30 June 1881 (Volume 49)
  - Day Book No. 3, 30 June 1881 - 1 October 1881 (Volume 50)
  - Day Book No. 4, 1 October 1881 - 31 December 1881 (Volume 51)
  - Day Book, 2 January 1882- 7 April 1882 (Volume 52)
  - Day Book, 8 April 1882 - 27 June 1882 (Volume 53)
  - Day Book No. 3, 27 June 1882 - 5 October 1882 (Volume 54)
  - Day Book, 20 September 1882 - 20 April 1885 (Volume 55)
  - Day Book, 5 October 1882 - 30 December 1882 (Volume 56)
  - Day Book, 1 January 1883 - 31 March 1883 (Volume 57)
  - Day Book, 19 March 1883 - 29 April 1884 (Volume 58)
  - Day Book No. 2, 1 March 1884 - 24 May 1884 (Volume 59)
  - Day Book, 11 August 1884 - 25 October 1884 (Volume 60)
  - Day Book No. 5, 27 October 1884 - 31 December 1884 (Volume 61)
  - Day Book, 1 January 1885 - 18 March 1885 (Volume 62)
  - Day Book, 19 March 1885 - 7 April 1885 (Volume 63)
  - Day Book No. 2, 25 March 1885 - 15 April 1885 (Volume 64)
  - Day Book, 1 January 1889 - 21 December 1889 (Volume 65)
  - Day Book, 1 January 1891 - 30 April 1891 (Volume 66)
  - Day Book, 1893-1894 (poor condition) (Volume 67)
  - Day Book, 1 May 1894 - 20 April 1895 (Volume 68)
  - Day Book, 1 May 1895 - 30 April 1896 (Volume 69)
  - Day Book, 1 May 1896 - 1 May 1897 (Volume 70)
  - Day Book, 1898-1900 (portion) (Volume 71)
  - Day Book, 1899-1902 (Volume 72)
  - Day Book, 1910-1914 (Volume 73)
  - Day Book, 13 February 1912 - 31 January 1913 (Volume 74)
  - Day Book, 3 July 1915 - 25 September 1915 (Volume 75)
  - Day Book, 27 September 1915 - 24 December 1915 (Volume 76)
  - Day Book, 25 December 1915 - 16 March 1916 (Volume 77)
  - Day Book, 17 March 1916 - 8 May 1916 (Volume 78)
  - Day Book, 8 May 1916 - 19 June 1916 (Volume 79)
  - Day Book, 19 June 1916 - 9 August 1916 (Volume 80)
  - Day Book, 12 August 1916 - 23 September 1916 (Volume 81)
  - Day Book, 23 November 1916 - 30 December 1916 (Volume 82)
  - Day Book No. 1, 1 January 1917 - 10 March 1917 (Volume 83)
  - Day Book, 10 March 1917 - 7 May 1917 (Volume 84)
  - Day Book, 8 May 1917 - 22 June 1917 (Volume 85)
  - Day Book, 4 August 1917 - 30 September 1917 (Volume 86)
  - Day Book, 1 October 1917 - 8 December 1917 (Volume 87)
  - Day Book, 10 December 1917 - 28 February 1918 (Volume 88)
  - Day Book, 1 March 1918 - 26 March 1918 (Volume 89)
  - Day Book, 8 April 1918 - 21 May 1918 (Volume 90)
  - Day Book, 15 July 1918 - 14 September 1918 (Volume 91)
  - Day Book, 16 September 1918 - 26 October 1918 (Volume 92)
  - Day Book, 28 October 1918 - 16 December 1918 (Volume 93)
  - Day Book, 1 January 1919 - 9 March 1919 (Volume 94)
  - Day Book, 10 March 1919 - 12 June 1919 (Volume 95)
  - Day Book, 19 June 1919 - 24 July 1919 (Volume 96)
  - Day Book, 24 July 1919 - 13 September 1919 (Volume 97)
  - Day Book, 6 September 1919 - 29 November 1919 (Volume 98)
  - Day Book, 1 December 1919 - 6 March 1920 (Volume 99)
  - Day Book, 6 March 1920 - 17 May 1920 (Volume 100)
  - Day Book, 18 May 1920 - 28 July 1920 (Volume 101)
  - Day Book, 29 July 1920 - 5 November 1920 (Volume 102)
  - Day Book, 1 January 1921 - 30 April 1921 (Volume 103)
  - Day Book, 2 May 1921 - 20 June 1921 (Volume 104)
  - Day Book, 14 September 1921 - 18 July 1922 (Volume 105)
  - Day Book B, 1 September 1927 - 19 May 1928 (Volume 106)
  - Day Book and Order Book No. 5, 1914-1915 (Volume 107)
  - Day Book and Order Book No. 6, 1915 (Volume 108)
  - Day Book and Order Book No. 7, 1915 (Volume 109)
  - Dover Farm Record Book, 1911-1916 (Volume 110)
  - Dover Farm Production, 1934 (Volume 111)
  - Dover Records, 1934-1936 (Volume 112)
  - Dover Farm - Receipts and Disbursements, 1935 (Volume 113)
  - Endless Bay Book, 1881-1882 (Volume 114)
  - Frying Pan and Endless Bay Headed Account Ledger, 1881-1882 (Volume 115)
  - Garden Record Book, 1916 (Volume 116)
  - Glencoe and Dover - Receipts and Disbursements, 1932-1934 (Volume 118)
  - Hands Book No. 2, 1869 (Volume 119)
  - Hands Book (Robert Baker), 1869-1870 (Volume 120)
  - Hands Book No. 1, 1873 (Volume 121)
  - Hands Book, 1874 (Volume 122)
  - Hands Book B, 1874 (Volume 123)
  - Hands Book, 1875 (Volume 124)
  - Hands Book A, 1876 (Volume 125)
  - Hands Book B, 1876 (Volume 126)
  - Hands Book, 1877 (Volume 127)
  - Hands Book B, 1877 (Volume 128)
  - Hands Book A, 1878 (Volume 129)
  - Hands Book B, 1878 (Volume 130)
  - Hands Book A, 1879 (Volume 131)
  - Hands Book B, 1879 (Volume 132)
  - Hands Book, 1880 (Volume 133)
  - Hands Book, 1880 (Volume 134)
  - Hands Book, 1881 (Volume 135)
  - Hands Book A, 1881 (Volume 136)
  - Hands Book, 1882 (Volume 137)
  - Hands Book A, 1882 (Volume 138)
  - Hands Book, 1882-1883 (Volume 139)
  - Hands Book, 1883 (Volume 140)
  - Hands Book A, 1883 (Volume 141)
  - Hands Book A, 1884 (Volume 142)
  - Hands Book B, 1884 (Volume 143)
  - Hands Book A, 1885 (Volume 144)
  - Hands Book A, 1885 (Volume 145)
  - Hands Book B, 1885 (Volume 146)
  - Hands Book A, 1886 (Volume 147)
  - Hands Book B, 1886 (Volume 148)
  - Hands Book, 1888 (Volume 149)
  - Hands Book, 1889 (Volume 150)
  - Hands Book, 1890 (Volume 151)
  - Hands Book, 1914-1915 (Volume 152)
  - Headed Accounts Ledger, 1873 (Volume 153)
  - Headed Accounts Ledger, 1874 (Volume 1)
  - Income Tax Report Data, 1919-1925 (Volume 154)
  - Job Book and Petty Accounts, 1912 (Volume 155)
  - Job Book and Petty Accounts, 1913 (Volume 156)
  - Job Book and Petty Accounts, 1914-1915 (Volume 6)
  - Job Book and Petty Accounts, 1915 (Volume 7)
  - Ledger, 1868 (Volume 157)
  - Ledger, 1879-1880 (Volume 158)
  - Ledger, 1880 (Volume 159)
  - Ledger, 1882 (Volume 160)
  - Ledger, 1882 (Volume 161)
  - Ledger, 1882-1883 (Volume 162)
  - Ledger, 1882-1883 (Volume 248)
  - Ledger, 1883 (Volume 163)
  - Ledger, 1887 (Volume 164)
  - Ledger, 1887 (Volume 165)
  - Ledger, 1887-1891 (Volume 166)
  - Ledger, 1889 (Volume 167)
  - Ledger, 1890 (Volume 168)
  - Ledger, 1893-1894 (Volume 169)
  - Ledger, 1897 (Volume 170)
  - Ledger, 1900-1901 (Volume 171)
  - Ledger, 1905-1906 (Volume 172)
  - Ledger, 1907-1910 (Volume 173)
  - Ledger No. 3, 1909-1910 (Volume 174)
  - Ledger, 1910-1914 (Wallace Brothers) (Volume 175)
  - Ledger No. 4, 1911 (Volume 176)
  - Ledger No. 5, 1912-1913 (Volume 177)
  - Ledger No. 6, 1913 (Volume 178)
  - Ledger, 1914-1915 (Volume 179)
  - Ledger, 1914-1915 (Volume 180)
  - Ledger (A. W. Willett), 1914-1915 (Volume 181)
  - Ledger, 1915-1916 (Volume 182)
  - Ledger, 1917 (Volume 183)
  - Ledger, 1918 (Volume 184)
  - Ledger, 1920-1921 (Volume 185)
  - Ledger, April 1921 (Volume 186)
  - Letter Book, 28 April 1883 - 8 August 1884 (Volume 187)
  - Letter Book, 9 August 1884 - 25 November 1884 (Volume 188)
  - Letter Book, 27 July 1887 - 9 September 1889 (Volume 189)
  - Letter Book, 1889-1892 (Volume 190)
  - Letter Book, 1892-1895 (Volume 191)
  - Letter Book, 1896-1907 (Volume 192)
  - Letter Book, 1898-1899 (Volume 193)
  - Letter Book, 20 August 1900 - 1 August 1902 (Wallace Brothers) (Volume 194)
  - Merchandise Day Book B, 1900-1903 (Volume 195)
  - Merchandise Day Book, 1901-1902 (Volume 196)
  - Merchandise Day Book, 1902-1903 (Volume 197)
  - Merchandise Day Book, 1903-1904 (Volume 198)
  - Merchandise Day Book, 1903-1907 (Volume 199)
  - Merchandise Day Book, 1904-1905 (Volume 200)
  - Merchandise Day Book, 1906-1907 (Volume 201)
  - Merchandise Day Book, 1907-1909 (Volume 202)
  - Merchandise Inventory Ledger, 1885-1889 (Volume 203)
  - Mill Time Book, 1884-1885 (Volume 204)
  - Money Order Cash Book, 1899-1909 (Volume 205)
  - Newsome's Book, July 1883 - May 1884 (Volume 206)
  - Pay Roll Ledger, ending 30 April 1899 (Volume 207)
  - Pay Roll, 1924 (Volume 208)